spreets.co.nz 2015-06-08

# Spreets - Privacy Policy

**(All capitalised terms are defined in the Spreetsterms and conditions).**

Our privacy policy covers the collection, dissemination and protection of information obtained from our website. We are committed to maintaining the privacy of all information provided by visitors to our website. No information will be collected without your consent and all such information will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### Collection of personal information

Membership Accounts contain personal information, comprising of each members' name, postal address, email address, gender and date of birth. 

We collect personal information as part of our effort to keep you informed about Spreets Deals that you may be interested in, to accept offers to purchase Spreets Deals and to confirm payment. We may also use the information to assist you to resolve a dispute, or issue you may have with, a Merchant or products or services provided by that Merchant and, where you raise an issue or dispute with us with respect to a Voucher or product or service, you authorise us to pass your personal information on to the Merchant as part of that process. We may also use the information to perform market research, plan future Spreets Deals, seek feedback and help make our website, products and services more useful to you. 

If you make an offer to purchase a Spreets Deal, you will need to provide your credit card details. We will use this information to process payment. Once your payment is processed we will email you a confirmation and a unique voucher code for redemption. If you do not provide us with your correct email address we will not be able to forward you your voucher. 

In the event that we merge, sell or otherwise change control of this website, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the personal information we have collected from you, without notice or consent. 

Apart from the above, we do not sell, lease or in any other way provide personally-identifying information to any other company, person or agency. 

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files placed by web browsers on a user's computer. Cookies are used to identify your activity on websites you visit. We may from time to time use cookies or similar devices to enhance the quality of the services provided by the website. In most circumstances, cookies will be optional and you may reject a cookie without significant impact on your accessibility to the function and the services provided on our website. All cookies placed by us will be for use by our website only. With the exception of any disclosure required by law, no information collected by us will be divulged or made available to any third party other than the merchant that you have purchased a voucher from, without your express consent. 

### Security

We work hard to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Layer Sockets (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last 4 digits of your credit card numbers when confirming subsequent orders. 

We take your data seriously. Our servers and processes for dealing with credit card information are PCI compliant. Your data is stored on secure servers and the servers are also in a secure environment with restricted access. 

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. 

### Unsolicited email

We recognise and appreciate the importance of responsible use of personal information. If you do not want the information that you provide to us to be used to inform you of other products and Spreets Deals and you indicate this preference when you provide the information to us, we will honour your preference. 

We will not use your email address to forward you information relating to any Spreets Deals or our products and services unless you have requested this information. 

### Opt Out

You may at any time opt out of receiving any further emails from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link of any emails that we have sent you. If you have any problems with opting out of any ongoing information service provided by us, please send an email to [support@spreets.co.nz](mailto:support@spreets.co.nz)

### Reviewing, updating or deleting your information

You are responsible for ensuring that your details remain current and accurate. If you wish to review, update or delete any information maintained by us about you, you may, where this information is made available to you by the website, directly update that information. In all other circumstances, please send an email to support@spreets.co.nz and we will provide you with full details as to all information we maintain in relation to you. We will also comply with any directions to update or delete any or all information. 

### Protection of information

When capturing customer data, it is passed through a secure server using encryption technology to ensure that your information is being protected when being sent over the Internet. 

Further, all stored information relating to members is protected from unauthorised access through the use of secure passwords and user log-ons or other security procedures.  
This website has security measures in place to avoid the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. We will protect any information we have concerning you in the same manner as we protect all our other confidential information. 

You should always close your browser and log out when you have finished surfing the net, to prevent others from accessing your personal information and correspondence. Beware of posting personal information in publicly accessible online forums, such as chat rooms. If you voluntarily disclose personal information it may be collected and used by others. 

By accessing or using this website, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy as outlined above. **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS WEBSITE**. We reserve the right at our discretion to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time. Any changes will be posted on the website. Please check this page from time to time for changes. 

### Contact Details

We are located at: 8b Target Court, Wairau Valley, Auckland 0627, New Zealand or submit a support ticket in our Support Center

* * *

## Spreets Commitment

We will always deal with you openly, honestly, and with integrity. If we mess-up (No, we're not perfect. Yet.) get in touch with us and we'll return your purchase. You can't say fairer than that. 

We value honesty. Tell us if you're not happy with our service, and we'll fix it. Mind you, that won't happen, because our service is outstanding and flawless. And since honesty is one of our core values, we must be telling the truth. 

We're in business to do the right thing by our customers and our clients. So we've made a conscious decision to trust you, and to remove as many obstacles as we can. We're trying to keep it simple, but if it's getting complicated please tell us. 

We want you to be able to tell people that your experience with Spreets has been a good experience. Even if we stuff up. We're human, so it may happen. So, if it does happen, just call us. We want to make it right. 

But remember we're only the piggy-in-the-middle! We're only acting on behalf of the business. Spreets is not the actual business. Don't shoot the messenger and all that jazz, especially if the messenger is us. The merchant should always be your first port of call if you have a query or concern about your experience. And because we only put nice people and great businesses on Spreets, we will help you resolve any issues you have when trying to redeem your offer. We're all about open, honest discussion, so if you want to learn more about our full terms and conditions they are right here. Yep, in broad daylight, for all to see. 

We want our Spreetsers to have nothing but best; the best experiences in the best cities with the best businesses, bar none. That includes your experience on our site and with our staff. If we're not up to scratch please tell us. We want to fix it for you. 

So there you are. It's a simple promise. And we will honour it. Expect nothing less from Spreets.
